www.addic7ed.com
Summoned to court to answer for
the crime of your bannerman,
Gregor Clegane, The Mountain.
Arrive within a fortnight
or be branded an enemy of the crown.
Poor Ned Stark. Brave man,
terrible judgement.
Attacking him was stupid.
Lannister...
don't act like fools.
You're gonna say
something clever?
Go on, say something clever.
Catelyn Stark took my brother.
Why is he still alive?
Tyrion?
Ned Stark.
One of our men interfered...
speared him through the leg,
before I could finish him.
Why is he still alive?
It wouldn't have been clean.
Clean?
You spent too much time
worrying about what other people think of you.
I could care less what
what anyone thinks of me.
That's what you want people
to think of you.
It's the truth.
And you hear them whispering "Kingslayer"
behind your back, doesn't it bother you?
Of course it bothers me.
A lion doesn't concern himself
with the opinion of a sheep.
I suppose I should be grateful
that your varity,
got in a way of your reckelessnes.
I'm giving you half of our forces.
30.000 men.
And we'll bring that to
Catelyn Stark girlhood home...
and remind her that Lannisters
pay their debts
I didn't realize you place such
a high value on my brother's life.
He's a Lannister.
Maybe the lowest of the Lannister,
but he's one of us.
And everyday that he remain a prisoner
the less our name command respect.
- So the lion does concern himself with the opinion...
- No, that's not an opinion, it's a fact.
If another house can seize
one of our own
and hold him captive, with impunity...
we are no longer house to be feared.
Your mother is dead.
Before long I'll be dead.
and you...
and your brother...
and your sister and all of her children...
all of us dead,
all of us rotting underground.
Is the family name
that lives on.
It's all that lives on.
Not your personal glory
not your honor... but family.
You understand?
You're blessed with ability
that few men possess.
You're blessed you belong to
the most powerful family in the kingdom.
And you still blessed
with youth.
And what you've done
with this blessing?
You served as the glorified bodyguard
for two kings..
One a mad man, the other are drunk.
The future of our family will be
determined in these next few months.
We could established a dinasty
that would last a thousand years...
or we could collapse into nothing.
As the Targaryen's did.
I need you to become a man
you're always meant to be.
Not next year, not tomorrow...
Now.
You're in pain.
I've had worse, my lady.
Perhaps it's time to go hoome.
The south doesn't seems to agree with you..
I knwo the truth Jon Arryn died for..
Do you, lord Stark?
Is that why you called me here?
To pose me riddles?
Has he done this before?
Jaime would've killed him.
My brother's worth
a thousand of your friend.
Your brother...
or your lover?
Targaryens wed brothers and sisters
for 300 years..
to keep bloodlines pure.
Jaime and I are more than
brother and sister.
We shared a womb.
Came to this world together,
we belong together.
My son saw you with him.
- Do you love your children?
- With all my heart.
- No more than I love mine.
- And they're all Jaime's.
Thank the Gods.
In the rare event that Robert leaves his whores
for long enough to stumble drunk into my bed,
I finished him off another ways
- In the morning he doesn't remember.
- You've always hated him.
Hated him?
I worshipped him.
Every girl in the southern kingdom
dreamt of him but he was mine by oath.
And when I finally saw him on our wedding day
in the Sept of Baelor.
lean and fierce, and black beared
it was the happiest moment of my life.
And that night he crawl on top of me,
stinking of wine
and did what he did what little he could do
and whispered in my ear : "Lyanna".
Your sister was a corpse
and I was a living girl
and he loved her more than me.
When the king return from his hunts,
I'll tell him the truth.
You must be gone by then...
you and your children.
I will not have that blood on my hands.
Go as far away as you can..
With as many men as you can.
Because wherever you go...
Robert's wrath will follow you.
And what of my wrath, lord Stark?
You should have taken the realm
for yourself.
Jaime told me about the day
King's Landing fell.
He was sitting in the Iron Throne
and you made him give it up.
All you needed to do is claim the step
yourself. Such a sad mistake.
I've made many mistakes in my life..
but that wasn't one of them.
Oh, but it was.
When you play the game of thrones,
you win or you die.
There is no middle ground.
No, No, No, No..
is that what they teach you
up in the North?
And you, wherever you're from.
Do you have any idea
how ridiculous you sound?
Either of you understand the thing that I'm saying?
Yes, my lord.
Lets start over. Shall we?
You be the man, and you be the woman.
Go ahead.
Slowly.
You're not fooling them,
they just paid you, they know what you are.
They know its all just an act
Your job is to make them
forget what they know.
And that takes time.
You need to..
ease into it.
Go ahead.
Ease into it.
He's winding you over,
inspite of yourself.
You starting to like this.
He wants to believe you.
He's enjoyed his cock since he was old enough
to play with a boy, shouldn't you?
He knows, he's better than other men.
He's always known it deep down inside
now he has proof.
He's so good...
he's reaching something deep inside of you
that no one even knew was there.
Overcoming your very nature..
Why don't you join us, my lord?
I'm saving myself for another.
What she doesn't know
will not hurt her?
A stupid saying..
What we don't know is usually
what get us killed.
She must be very beautiful.
No, not really.
Impeccable bloodlines, though.
I do believe my lord in love.
For many years.
Most of my life really.
Play with her ass.
And she loved me too.
I was her little confidant.
A play thing. She could tell me anything,
anything at all.
She told me about
all the horses that she liked.
The castle that she want to live in.
The man that she wanted to marry.
A northener..
with a jaw like an anvil.
So I challenged him to a duel. I mean,
why not? I'd read all the stories.
The little hero always beats
the big villain in all the stories.
In the end...
she wouldn't even let him kill me.
"He's just a boy", she said.
"Please don't hurt him".
So he gave me a nice little scar to remember
and by enough they went
- And she still married to him?
- Oh, no.
He got himself killed before the wedding.
And she ended up with his brother,
an even more impressive spciment.
She love him, I'm afraid.
And why wouldn't she, I mean?
Who could compare to him,
he just so...
good.
Do you know what I learned
losing that duel?
I learned that I'll never win.
Not that way.
That's their game.
Their rules.
I'm not going to fight them.
I'm going to fuck them.
That's what I know, that's what I am.
And only by admitting what we are,
can we get what we want.
And what do you want?
Oh, everything, my dear.
Everything there is.
Now wash yourself,
both of you are working tonight.
You're very lucky girl,
do you know that?
Where I come from we don't show mercy
to criminals.
Where I come from,
if someone like you attacked a little lord..
the low tide will lay you on your back,
on the beach..
your hands and feet chained to four stakes..
sea will coming cloaser and closer.
You'll see death creeping toward you,
a few inches at a time.
Where do you come from?
The Iron Islands.
They far away?
You've never heard of the Iron Islands?
Trust me, you've never heard
where I'm from neither.
Trust me, my lord.
You're not living in the wilderness anymore.
In civilised land, you advert
your betters by their proper titles.
And what's that?
Lord.
Why?
What do you mean "why"?
My father is Balon Greyjoy,
lord of the Iron Islands.
What's that got to do with you?
Your father's lord,
how can you be lord too?
- I will be lord after my father..
- So you're not lord now.
No, you...
You having a go at me?
Is that it?
Just don't understand
how you southerner do things.
I'm not a southerner.
You're from south of The Wall...
that make you southerner to me.
You're an impudent little wench,
aren't you?
Couldn't say, my lord.
Didn't know what impunent means.
Impudent. It means rude.
Disrespectful.
Do you want to loose that chain?
Theon Greyjoy!
The lady is our guest.
Thought she was our prisoner.
Are the two mutually exclusive,
in your experience?
Chances are I won't be nearby
the next time that happens.
I'm used to worst than him.
I'm used to men
that can chew that boy up.
And pick their teeth with his bones.
Why did you come here?
Didn't mean to come here.
Meant to get much further south
than this. As far as south as south goes.
Before the long night comes.
Why?
What do you afraid of?
Those thing that sleep in the day
and hunt at night
- Owl and shadowcats...
- I'm not talking about owl and shadowcats.
The thing you speak of..
have been gone for thousand of years.
It wasn't gone, old man.
They were sleeping.
And they're sleeping no more.
I missed girls.
Not even talking to them,
I never talk to them.
Just lookin' at them.
Hearing them giggle.
Don't you missed girls?
Riders!
The horn. We have to blow the horn.
Why is he alone?
One blast for a ranger returning
Two for wildlings
- Three..
- He's no rider.
That's my uncle Benjen rode..
where's my uncle?
Ned!
Robert...
we are hunting... a boar...
I should have spent more time with you.
Shown to you how to be a man.
I was never meant to be a father.
Go on....
you don't want to see this.
My fault..
Too much wine..
Missed my thrust..
Stinks.
Stinks like death.
Don't think I can't smell it.
Pay the bastard back, Ned.
I drove my knife
right through his brain
You ask him if I didn't. Ask him!
I want the funeral feast to be the biggest
the kingdom ever saw..
And I want everyone
to taste the boar that got me
Now leave us, the lot of you
I need to talk to Ned.
- Robert, my sweet...
- Out! All of you!
You damn fool.
Paper and ink. On the table.
Write down what I said.
In the name of Robert
of the House Baratheon
First of... you know how it goes.
Put in the damn titles..
I hereby command..
Eddard of House Stark...
titles..titles...
to serve as Lord Regent and Protector of The Realm, upon my death..
to rule in my stead..
until my son Joffrey comes of age.
Give it over..
Give it to the council..
after I'm death.
At least they'll say I did this right, this one thing.
You'll rule now.
You'll hate it worse than I did..
but you'll do it well.
The girl..
Daenerys...
you're right.
Varys, Littlefinger, my brother..
Worthless..
Noone to tell me "No" but you.
Only you.
Let her live
- Stop it if its not to late.
- I will.
My son...
help him, Ned.
Make him better than me
I'll...
I'll do everything I can
to honor your memory.
My memory?
King Robert Baratheon...
murdered by a pig.
Give me something to the pain,
and let me die.
Give him milk of the poppy.
He was reeling from the wine..
He commanded us to...
step aside, but...
I failed him.
No men could've protected him from himself.
I wonder, Ser Barristan,
who gave the King this wine?
His squire.
From the King's own skin.
His squire? The Lannister boy?
Such a dutiful boy to make sure
His Grace did not lack refreshment.
I do hope the poor lad
is not blame himself.
His Grace has had a change of heart
concerning Daenerys Targaryen.
Whatever arrangements you made...
unmade them, at once.
I'm afraid those birds have flown.
The Khaleesi likely dead already.
Can you help me make him.. understand?
The Dothraki do things on their own time
for their own reason
Have patience, Khaleesi. We will
go home, I promise you.
My brother...
was a fool, I know.. but he was
the rightful heir to the Seven Kingdoms.
Have I said something funny, ser?
Forgive me, khaleesi, but your ancestor,
Aegon The Conqueror,
didn't seize six of the kingdoms
because it his right.
He have no right to them,
he seized them because he could.
And because he had dragons.
Having few dragons makes things easier.
- You don't believe it?
- Have you ever seen a dragon, khaleesi?
I believe what my eyes and ears report.
As for the rest, it was 300 years ago,
who knows what really happened.
Now if you pardon me,
I'll seek out the merchant captain..
- see if he has any letter for me.
- Well, I'll come with you.
No, no, don't trouble yourself.
Enjoy the market.
I'll rejoin you soon enough.
Jorah, the Andal?
The Spider sent his greetings
and his congratulations.
Overall pardon,
you can go home now.
My son already has his name, but I'll
try your summer wine. Just a taste.
My lady, you are from Westeros?
You have the honor of addressing
Daenerys of the House Targaryen.
Khaleesi of the riding men,
and princess of the Seven Kingdoms.
- Princess.
- Rise.
I still like to taste that wine.
That?
Dorne's sweet not worthy of a princess.
I have the dry red from the Arbor.
Nectar of the Gods.
Let me give you a cask.
- A gift!
- You honor me, ser.
The honor.. the honor is all mine.
You know there are many in your homeland
that pray for your return, princess.
I hope to repay your kindness someday.
The wine is for the Khaleesi,
it's not for the likes of you.
Open it.
Pour.
It would be a crime to drink a wine this rich
without at least giving it time to breathe.
Do as he says.
As the princess command.
Sweet, isn't it?
Can you smell the fruit, ser?
Taste it, my lord.
Tell me that is not the finest wine
that has ever touch your tongue.
You first.
Me?
I'm afraid I'm not worthy of the vintage.
Beside, is it a poor wine merchant
who drink up his own wares
You will drink.
Come.
You came to us as outlaws..
poachers..
rapers..
killers, thieves...
You came alone..
in chains..
without friends, or honor.
You came to us rich..
or you came to us poor.
Some of you bear the name
of proud houses..
all those only bastard names,
or no names at all.
It does not matter.
All that, is in the past.
Here..
on the Wall.
we're all one house.
Tonight..
We're allowed to look happy..
you're going to be a ranger.
It's not what you always wanted?
I want to find my uncle.
I know he's alive out there.
I know he is.
I wish I could help you,
but I'm no ranger.
its the steward's life for me.
You're honored being a steward.
Not much, really.
But those food.
You begin a new.
A man of the Night's Watch.
live his life for the realm.
Not for King
or a Lord..
or the honor of this house or that house.
Not for gold, glory,..
or women's love.
But for the realm..
and all the people in it.
You all learned the words, your vow
Think carefully before you say them.
The penalty for desertion..
is death.
You can take your vows here..
tonight..
at sunset.
Do any of you still keep the Old Gods?
I do, my lord.
Do you want to take your vows before the heart tree,
as your uncle did?
Yes, my lord.
You'll find the weirwoods,
a mile north of the Wall..
and your Old  Gods too, maybe.
My Lord?
Might I go as well?
Is House Tarly keep the Old Gods?
No, my lord..
I was name in the light of the Seven..
as my father was
and his father before him.
Why would you forsake,
the Gods of your father and your house?
The Night's Watch is my house now.
The Seven have never answer my prayers..
perhaps the Old Gods will.
As you wish.
You all been,
assigned an order..
according to our needs..
and your strength.
Halder, builders.
Pyp, to the stewards.
Tod, to the builders.
Grenn, to the rangers.
Samwell, to the stewards.
Matthar, to the rangers.
Dareon, to the stewards.
Ballion, to the rangers
Rast, to the rangers
Jon, to the stewards.
Lancel, to the builders.
Ihyll, to the builders.
Gordor, to the stewards.
Nikko, to the rangers.
Eskan, to the rangers.
Albett, to the builders,
Jorden to the stables.
Mikken, to the cooks.
Halor, to the builders.
Delugo, to the rangers.
May all the Gods preserve you.
Rangers, with me.
Builders!
Samwell...
you will assisst me in the rookery
and the library.
Pyp...
you will report to Bowen Marsh,
in the kitchen.
Luke, report to One Eye Joe in the stable..
Dareon, I'm sending you to the east watch..
present yourself to Borcas when you arrive..
Make no comment about his nose.
Jon Snow...
Lord Commander Mormont has requested you
for his personal steward.
Will I serve the Lord Commander's meal,
and fetch hot water for his bath?
Certainly.
And keep the fire burning in his chambers..
change his sheets
and blankets daily..
and do everything else the Lord Commander requires of you.
You take me for a servant?
We took you for a man of the Night's Watch.
But perhaps we were wrong in that.
May I go?
As you wish.
Jon! Wait!
- Don't you see what they're doing?
- I see ser Alliser revenge thats all..
he wanted it and he got it.
Steward are nothing
but maid!
I'm a better swordman and rider than any of you!
It's not fair!
Fair?
I was singing for a high lord
at Acorn Hall,
when he put his hand in my leg
and he wanted to see my cock.
I pushed him away and he said..
he'd have my hand cut off
for stealing when he's over.
So now I'm here,
at the end of the world,
where noone to sing a folk,
but old men and little shit like you.
I'll never see my family again.
I'll never been inside a women again.
Don't tell me about fair.
I thought you were caught stealing
a wheel of cheese..
for your starving sister.
Course who's gonna teel a bunch of strangers..
a high lord try to grab my cock?
Could you sing me a song, Pyp?
I'd like to hear a song.
Now listen to me..
the old man, is the Lord Commander
of The Night's Watch.
You will be with him, day and night,
yes.. you will clean his clothes.
You will also, take his letters..
attend him at meeting,
squire for him at battle.
You'll know everything,
be part of everything.
And he ask for you himself.
He wants to groom you for command.
I just...
I always wanted to be a ranger.
I always wanted to be a wizard.
What?
No, I'm serious.
So you'll stay and say your word with me?
Lord Stark.
A moment?
Alone, if you will.
He name you Protector of The Realm.
He did.
She won't care.
Give me an hour and I'll put
a hundred of swords at your command.
- And what should I do with a hundred swords?
- Strike!
Tonight, while the castle sleeps.
We must get Joffrey away from his mother
and into our custody.
Protector of The Realm or no,
he who holds the king holds the kingdom.
Every moment you delay,
gives Cersei another moment to prepare.
By the time Robert die,
it would be late for the both of us.
What about Stannis?
Saving the Seven Kingdoms from Cersei
and delivering him to Stannis?
You have odd notion about
"protecting the realm".
Stannis is your older brother.
This isn't about the bloody line of succession.
That didn't matter when you rebelled
against the Mad King..
it shouldn't matter now.
What's the best for the kingdoms?
What's best for the people we rule?
We all know what Stannis is..
He inspires no love, or loyalty.
He's not a king.
I am.
Stannis is a commander.
He's led men into war, twice.
- He destroyed the Greyjoy fleet.
- Yes. he's a good soldier, everyone knows that.
so is Robert.
Tell me something. Do you still believe
good soldier made good king?
I will not dishonor Robert's last hour
by shedding blood in his house..
and dragging frightened children,
from their beds.
You will sail to Dragonstone tonight.
You will place this in the hand of Stannis Baratheon.
Not his steward.
Not his captain of the guard.
And not his wife.
Only Stannis himself.
Yes, my lord.
Now leave us.
My lord protector.
The king has no trueborn son.
Joffrey and Tommen, are Jaime Lannister's bastards.
- So when the king dies..
- The throne passes to his brother..
Lord Stannis.
So it would seem.
- Unless..
- There is no "unless"!
He is the rightful heir.
Nothing can change that.
And he cannot take the throne
without your help.
You would be wise to denied to him.
And to make sure Joffrey succeeds.
Do you have a shred of honor?
You're now Hand of The King
and Protector of The Realm,
all the power is yours, you need only..
reach out and take it.
Make peace with the Lannisters.
Release The Imp.
Wed your daughter to Joffrey.
We've plenty of time
to get rid of Stannis..
and if Joffrey seems likely to cause problems
when he come into his throne..
we simply reveal his little secret..
- and sit Lord Renly there instead.
- We?
You'll need someone to share this burdens,
I assure you..
my price would be modest.
Would you suggest this treason?
Only if we lose.
Make peace with the Lannisters you say..
The people who tried to murder my boy.
We only make peace with our enemy, my lord.
That's why its called making peace.
No...
I won't do it.
- So it will be Stannis? and war?
- There is no other choice.
He is the heir.
So why did you call me here?
Not for my wisdom clearly.
You promised Catelyn
you would help me.
The queen had a dozen knights
and hundred man-at-arms.
Enough to overwhelm what remain
of my household guard.
I need the Gold Cloaks.
The City Watch is two thousand strong.
and sworn to defend the king's peace.
Look at you.
You know what you want me to do.
You know it has to be done.
But it's not honorable, so...
the words stick in your throat.
When the Queen proclaims one king,
and the Hand proclaim another..
who's peace to the Gold Cloaks protect?
Who do they follow?
The man who pays them.
Hear my words,
and bear witness to my vow
Night gathers, and now my watch begins.
It shall not end until my death.
I shall take no wife, hold no lands, father no children.
I shall wear no crowns and win no glory.
I shall live and die at my post.
I am the sword in the darkness.
I am the watcher on the walls.
I am the shield that guards the realm of men.
I pledge my life and honor to the Night's Watch,
for this night and all the nights to come.
You knelt as boys..
rise now as men
of the Night's Watch.
Welcome.. Welcome..
What he's got there?
To me, Ghost.
Bring it here.
Gods be good.
What will they do to him?
When the khalasar rides..
he'll be leashed to the saddle and forced
to run behind the horses, as long as he can.
And when he falls?
I saw a man last nine miles once.
King Robert still wants me dead.
This poisoner was the first,
he won't be the last.
I thought he'd leave me alone,
now that my brother is gone.
He will never leave you alone.
If you ride to Asshai,
his assassins will follow you.
If you sail all the way to the Basilisk Isle,
his spy would tell him.
He will never abandon the hunt.
You are Targaryen.
The last Targaryen.
Your son will have Targaryen blood..
with 40.000 riders behind him.
He will not have my son.
He will not have you either, khaleesi.
Lord Stark!
- Stop!
- It's alright.
- It's alright. Let him through.
- Lord Stark...
King Joffrey and the queen regent
request you presence in the throne room.
King Joffrey?
King Robert is gone.
The Gods give him rest.
All is accomplished.
The City Watch is youts.
Good.
Is Lord Renly joining us?
I fear Lord Renly
has left the city.
He rode through the Old Gate
an hour before dawn..
with ser Loras Tyrell
and some fifty retainers.
Last seen galloping south in some haste.
We stand behind you, lord Stark.
All hail His Grace,
Joffrey of Houses Baratheon and Lannister.
The First of His Name,
The King of The Andal, and The First Men..
Lord of The Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of The Realm.
I command the council to make all necessary arrangements for my coronation.
I wish to be crowned within the forthnight.
Today I shall accept oaths of fealty
from my loyal councillors.
Ser Barristan...
I believe no men here
could ever question your honor.
King Robert seal.
Unbroken.
Lord Eddard Stark is herein named..
Protector of The Realm..
to rule as regent...
until the heir come of age.
May I see that letter, ser Barristan?
Protector of The Realm.
Is this meant to be your shield,
Lord Stark?
A piece of paper.
Those were the king's words.
We have a new king now.
Lord Eddard, when we last spoke
you offer me some counsel.
Allow me to return the courtesy.
Bend the knee, my lord.
Bend the knee
and swear loyalty to my son.
And we shall allow you to live out the days
in the grey waste..
you called home.
Your son has no claim to the throne.
Liar!
You condemn yourself
with your own mouth, Lord Stark.
Ser Barristan, seize this traitor.
Ser Barristan is a good man,
a loyal man, do him no harm.
You think you stands alone?
Kill him! Kill all of them.
I commanded.
Commander!
Take the queen and
her children to custody.
Escort them back to the royal apartment
and keep them there under guard.
Men of the watch!
I want no bloodshed.
Tell your men to lay down their swords,
noone needs to die.
Now!
I did warn you not to trust me.
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net