You did this.
You did this!
- We have to leave.
- Cersei: Take him! Take him!
Where is his wife?
Where's Sansa?
Find her.
Bar the gates of the city.
Seize every ship in the harbor.
- Where is she?!
- No one leaves the capital!
No one!
( bells tolling )
- Get in.
- Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
Up you go, my lady.
You'll be fine.
You're stronger than you know.
( gasps )
- Lord Baelish?
- Petyr.
Are you hurt, my lady?
Good. Good.
I'm sure you've had quite a fright.
Rest easy.
- The worst is past.
- Dontos: Lord Baelish.
- I promised I'd get her to you safely.
- Softly, my friend.
Voices carry over water.
I should get back before
someone thinks to look for me.
First you'll want your pay.
- 10,000 was it?
- 10,000.
( snaps fingers )
Wait!
( groans )
( screams )
Littlefinger:  Shh.
You don't want the
queen to hear, do you?
1,000 gold cloaks
are searching for you.
And if they found you,
how do you think they would punish
the girl who murdered the king?
- I didn't murder anyone.
- I know. I know.
But you must admit
it looks suspicious.
The king who
executed your father,
who tormented you for years,
and you fled the scene
of his murder.
Why did you kill him?
Because he was
a drunk and a fool
and I don't trust drunk fools.
He saved me.
Saved you? My lady,
he followed my orders.
Every one of them.
And he did it all for gold.
Money buys a man's
silence for a time.
A bolt in the heart
buys it forever.
He was helping me
because I saved his life.
Yes, and he gave you
a priceless necklace
that once belonged
to his grandmother.
The last legacy
of House Hollard.
I had it made a few weeks ago.
What did I once tell
you about the capital?
We're all liars here.
Come, my lady.
I know you've had
a difficult day.
But you're safe now.
I promise you that.
You're safe with me
and sailing home.
So am I the queen?
More than you were with Renly.
Less than you would have been if
Joffrey had done you the courtesy
of consummating
the marriage before dying.
In any case, this would
not be an opportune moment
to press the issue.
Clawing at his own throat,
looking to his mother to make
it stop-- it was horrible.
The world is overflowing
with horrible things.
But they're all a tray
of cakes next to death.
They brought me your grandfather's
body when he died, you know?
Made me look at it.
What was it like?
They took me to the Great
Hall and there he was.
The man I'd married
and suffered to father
my children.
A great doughy lump
I'd sat next to
at endless dinners
and tedious gatherings.
There he was...
lying on a table.
One of my husbands
preferred the company of men
and was stabbed
through the heart.
Another was happiest
torturing animals
and was poisoned
at our wedding feast.
- I must be cursed.
- Nonsense.
Your circumstances
have improved markedly.
You may not have enjoyed
watching him die,
but you enjoyed it more
than you would have enjoyed
being married to him,
I can promise you that.
But I would have been the queen.
Our alliance with the Lannisters
remains every bit
as necessary to them
as it is unpleasant for us.
You did wonderful
work on Joffrey.
The next one should be easier.
Tywin:
Your brother is dead.
Do you know what that means?
I'm not trying to trick you.
It means I'll become king.
Yes, you will become king.
What kind of king
do you think you'll be?
A good king?
Mm, I think so as well.
You've got the right
temperament for it.
But what makes
a good king? Hmm?
What is a good king's single
most important quality?
This is hardly
the place or the time.
Holiness?
Hmm.
Baelor the Blessed was holy.
And pious.
He built this sept.
He also named a six-year-old
boy high septon
because he thought the boy
could work miracles.
He ended up fasting
himself into an early grave
because food was of this world
and this world was sinful.
Justice.
Yeah.
A good king must be just.
Orys I was just.
Everyone applauded his reforms.
Nobles and commoners alike.
But he wasn't just for long.
He was murdered in his sleep
after less than a year
by his own brother.
Was that truly just of him?
To abandon his subjects
to an evil
that he was too gullible
to recognize?
- No.
- What about strength?
- Yes.
Strength.
King Robert was strong.
He won the rebellion
and crushed
the Targaryen dynasty.
And he attended three
small council meetings
in 17 years.
He spent his time whoring
and hunting and drinking
until the last two killed him.
So, we have a man who
starves himself to death,
a man who lets his own
brother murder him,
and a man who thinks that winning
and ruling are the same thing.
What do they all lack?
- Wisdom.
- Yes!
Wisdom is what
makes a good king.
Yes.
But what is wisdom?
Hmm?
A house with great wealth
and fertile lands
asks you for your protection
against another house
with a strong navy
that could one day oppose you.
How do you know which choice
is wise and which isn't?
You've any experience
of treasuries and granaries
or shipyards and soldiers?
- No.
- No. Of course not.
A wise king knows what he
knows and what he doesn't.
You're young.
A wise young king listens
to his counselors
and heeds their advice
until he comes of age.
And the wisest kings
continue to listen to them
long afterwards.
Your brother was not
a wise king.
a good king.
If he had been,
perhaps he'd still be alive.
Now, as the king,
you will have to marry.
Do you understand why?
Tommen:
A king needs a queen.
Tywin:
Yes, but why?
To further the family line.
- Do you know how that happens?
- Yes.
Yes, but has anyone explained
the details to you?
I don't think so.
It's all relatively
straightforward.
- How are you?
- I'm all right.
You are.
You will be.
I'll see to that.
Please give the queen
a moment alone with her son.
- Yes, my lord.
- All of you.
( snaps fingers )
( doors echo shut )
It was Tyrion.
He killed him.
He told me he would.
"A day will come when you
think you are safe and happy
and your joy will turn
to ashes in your mouth."
That's what he said to me.
You saw it.
You saw Joff point at him
just before he--
I don't know what I saw.
Avenge him.
Avenge our son.
Kill Tyrion.
Tyrion's my brother.
Our brother.
There'll be a trial. We'll get
to the truth of what happened.
I don't want a trial.
He'll squirm his way to
freedom given the chance.
I want him dead.
( crying )
Please, Jaime.
You have to.
He was our son.
Our baby boy.
( gasps )
You're a hateful woman.
Why have the gods made
me love a hateful woman?
Jaime, not here, please.
Please.
- ( fabric rips )
- Stop it.
- Stop it. Stop.
- No.
Stop it.
Stop.
- Stop. It's not right.
- ( Grunts )
It's not right.
- I don't care.
- ( Crying )
- Don't.
- I don't care.
- Don't. Jaime, don't.
( thunder rumbles )
Gonna rain soon.
( urinating )
Where are we?
Near Fairmarket, I think.
You think?
You don't have a map?
-  No, I don't have a map.
- Maybe we should get one.
Just point out the next map shop
you see and I'll buy you one.
How far is it to the Eyrie?
- Far.
- And you're sure we're going the right way?
Believe me, girl, I want you
there as soon as I can.
Get my gold, be on my way.
- On your way where?
- Why do you care?
Might book passage
across the Narrow Sea.
Fight as a sellsword.
Second Sons, could be.
Seems like a good fit for me.
I'd like to see Braavos one day.
Why Braavos?
I have friends there.
( blows )
I doubt it.
Seven blessings to you.
- What do you want?
- What do I want? This is my land.
If I'm standing on it,
it's my land.
We were just watering the horses.
We'll be on our way.
Forgive my father.
He was wounded fighting
in the war.
Our cottage burned down while he
was gone and my mother with it.
He's never been the same.
Which house did he fight for?
The Tullys of Riverrun.
There's a storm coming.
You'll be wanting
a roof tonight.
There's fresh hay in the barn.
And Sally here makes rabbit stew
just like her mom used to do.
We don't have much,
but any man that bled
for House Tully
is welcome to it.
-  ( thunder rumbling )
-  ( Rain pattering )
Man:  We ask the Father
to judge us with mercy
accepting our human frailty.
We ask the Mother
to bless our crops
so we may feed ourselves
and all who come to our door.
We ask the Warrior
to give us courage
in these days of strife
and turmoil.
We ask the Maiden
to protect Sally's virtue
to keep her from
the clutches of depravity.
You got to do
all seven of the fuckers?
Father!
We ask the Smith
to strengthen our hands
and our backs so we may finish
the work required of us.
We ask the Crone to guide us on our
journey from darkness to darkness.
And we ask the Stranger
not to kill us
in our beds tonight
for no damn reason at all.
I'm so sorry.
( slurping loudly )
Really good.
- Did you fight at the Twins?
- Call that a fight?
Slaughtering livestock
more like.
The Red Wedding
they're calling it.
Walder Frey committed
sacrilege that day.
He shared bread and salt with the Starks.
He offered them guest right.
Guest right
don't mean much anymore.
It means something to me.
The gods will have
their vengeance.
Frey will burn in the seventh
hell for what he did.
Things were different when Hoster
Tully ruled the Riverlands.
We had good years and bad
years, same as anyone.
But we were safe.
Now with the Freys,
raiders come plundering, steal
our food, steal our silver.
I was gonna send Sally north
to stay with my brother,
but the north's no better.
The whole country's gone sour.
You got any ale?
Afraid not.
How can a man
not keep ale in his home?
You look like you could
really swing that sword.
A real warrior
with proper training.
Those raiders wouldn't
stand a chance against you.
How would it be if you stayed
on till the new moon?
I could use a man to help
with the farmwork.
Sally does what she can,
but she can't lift
a bale of hay.
And if any thieves came
looking for easy pickings,
one look at you, I'd bet
they'd run the other way.
Meaning no offense.
What'll you pay?
I don't have much.
But I have hidden a bit of
silver from the bandits.
Fair wages for fair work?
Fair wages for fair work.
( chickens clucking )
( faint voices arguing )
-  ( punch lands )
-  ( Man groans )
( girl screams )
( man groaning )
- What did you do?!
-  Get your horse saddled.
- You told me you weren't a thief.
- I wasn't.
He took us in.
He fed us and you--
Aye, he took us in.
He's a good man
and his daughter makes
a nice stew.
And they'll both
be dead come winter.
- You don't know that.
- I do know it.
He's weak.
He can't protect himself.
They'll both be dead
come winter.
Dead men don't need silver.
You're the worst shit
in the Seven Kingdoms.
There's plenty worse than me.
I just understand
the way things are.
How many Starks they got to
behead before you figure it out?
Ranger:
Raper. Raper.
Horse thief.
Ninth born son.
Raper.
Thief.
Thief and raper.
There he is, Sam the Slayer.
Going to visit
your wildling whore?
- She's not a whore.
- No?
Maybe I'll give her a copper
tonight and find out.
They all think I'm lying.
About what?
Killing the white walker.
You're not lying.
I'll never forget
the way it screamed.
But you're the only one
that saw it.
And they all think
you're just a--
A what?
Well, a wildling.
My father hated that word.
It's not a very nice word,
I suppose.
I don't know.
It makes me sound a bit
dangerous, doesn't it?
So...
are you all right?
No one bothering you?
I get a lot of looks.
I hear them making their jokes.
But no one's touched me
if that's what you mean.
I worry about it sometimes.
All the time.
Why do you worry about it?
100 men, one woman.
I've got other things
to think about.
That's the only thing
they think about.
- You're being silly.
- I'm not being silly.
There's 100 men lying awake
at night picturing you.
What about you?
What about me?
Gilly?
I worry about you.
Thank you.
For what?
For worrying about me.
I don't know
if you're safe here.
They're my brothers,
but some of them were thieves
before they came here.
Some of them were rapers.
You saw what they did
at your father's keep.
So what are you saying?
Maybe you'd be safer
in Mole's Town.
Are you bored of me?
Bored of you?
I...
I want to protect you.
I'll get these to Hobb.
Keep an eye on little Sam.
( door closes )
( thunder rumbling )
Your Grace.
You're a literary man now.
What do you make of that?
- Joffrey?
- The usurper Joffrey Baratheon.
I said those words when I
tossed a leech into the fire.
A leech filled with
bastard blood.
A bastard you set free.
I am now faced with
a great opportunity
and I am powerless
to take advantage of it.
I will find you
an army, Your Grace.
- I've been working day and night--
- What progress have you made?
I've rallied House Peasebury
to your cause.
House Peasebury.
- House Musgood.
- And House Haigh.
- House Haigh.
( pieces clatter )
They don't have enough men
between them to raid a pantry.
Westeros is not
the world, Your Grace.
We need to look east
for ships and men.
10,000 skilled soldiers
fight for the Golden Company.
- The Golden Company?
- They've never broken a contract.
They're sellswords.
We're willing to use blood magic
to put you on the throne,
but we're not willing
to pay men to fight?
Now the Red Woman's
magic is real.
Her visions and prophecies
may be, too,
but I've never heard of visions
and prophecies winning a war.
Soldiers win wars.
Soldiers on the ground.
It's dirty on the ground.
We don't have any gold.
Not yet.
If I do not press my claim,
my claim will be forgotten.
I will not become a page in
someone else's history book.
I'm running out
of time, Ser Davos.
Which means you're
running out of time.
( knocking )
You're late.
I'm sorry, Princess.
I thought you weren't coming.
The Hand of the King doesn't
have much leisure time.
You won't be a very good Hand if you see
the word knight and say "ka-nigit."
That happened once, weeks ago.
You're your father's
daughter, no mistake.
Bloody relentless,
the both of you.
It's a new one today.
Lots of tricky words.
But I think you can manage.
You'll never read well
if you move your lips.
That's how children do it.
"The Life and Adventures
of Elyo Grivas
First Sword of Braavos."
- ( claps )
- Thank you very much.
I like this one. It's full
of sword fights and pirates.
You were a pirate once.
No, I was never a pirate.
I was a smuggler.
What's the difference?
Well, if you're
a famous smuggler,
you're not doing it right.
My father says
a criminal is a criminal.
Your father lacks
an appreciation
of the finer points
of bad behavior.
So do the Braavosi.
- You've sailed to Braavos?
- Of course.
Almost got beheaded
by a First Sword of Braavos.
I tried to explain to him the difference
between pirates and smugglers,
but he didn't seem any more interested
in the distinction than your father.
I suppose if you work
for the Iron Bank of Braavos
and each one of your gold
barges is worth half a kingdom,
you tend not to be overly concerned
with the kind of distinction--
- What was that for?
- I need you to write a message.
You should write it yourself.
It's good practice.
It's too important for me.
I need a smart person
to do it. Go on.
To the offices
of the Iron Bank of Braavos
from Stannis Baratheon the
one true king of Westeros.
But that's not you.
I need to get their attention.
Go on. Write.
( baby cooing )
He's seen some
adventures, hasn't he?
( people laughing, chatting )
- Precious little thing.
- Thank you.
- What's his name?
- Sam.
Lovely.
That the daddy?
No.
Where's the daddy?
He's dead.
Oh. Where you from?
North of here.
North of here?
You a fucking wildling?
- Only room and board?
- That's right.
She'll clean and cook
and look after the other
girls' babies.
Could find other
work for her, too.
- No other work.
- There'd be money.
Give you a piece of it.
No other work.
I promise to come back
and visit whenever I can.
You'll be safer here.
Who's gonna protect you
at Castle Black? Me?
You protected me
north of the Wall.
This is different.
They're brothers
of the Night's Watch
and I can't just stab
them in the back
and I can't run away, which
is what we did at Craster's.
( baby crying )
You have to trust me.
It's for the best.
Best for you.
Oh, Gilly.
Please don't.
( baby crying )
( moaning )
Greedy.
No?
I'm sorry.
You're lovely,
I just never acquired the taste.
You're calling my beauty
an acquired taste?
That's quite all right, lover.
It's more for you.
Your loss.
You like them both the same?
- Boys and girls?
- Does that surprise you?
Everyone has a preference.
Then everyone is missing
half the world's pleasure.
The gods made that
and it delights me.
The gods made this
When it comes to war,
I fight for Dorne.
When it comes to love,
I don't choose sides.
I hope I have as much
stamina when I'm your age.
What are you, 25?
- Children.
- ( Chuckles )
Someday, if you're lucky,
you will wake up
and realize you are old.
That pretty ass
of yours will sag.
Your belly will grow soft and
your back will ache in the night
and gray hairs will sprout
from your ears.
No one will want you anymore.
Make sure you fucked
your fill before that day.
Did you?
He is a prince of Dorne.
Girls and boys will line up
to fuck him
till the day he dies.
They will all have
to line up behind you.
( door opens )
-  Prince Oberyn.
- Lord Tywin.
May we have the room?
Call my name
if you need me, lover.
Would you like to sit?
No, thank you.
Some wine?
( door closes )
- I'm sorry about your grandson.
- Are you?
I don't believe that a child is
responsible for the sins of his father.
Or his grandfather.
An awful way to die.
Which way is that?
Are you interrogating
me, Lord Tywin?
Some believe the king choked.
Some believe the sky
is blue because we live
inside the eye
of a blue-eyed giant.
The king was poisoned.
I hear you studied
poisons at the Citadel.
I did.
This is why I know.
Your hatred for my family
is rather well known.
You arrive at the capital,
an expert in poisoning,
some days later my grandson
dies of poisoning.
Rather suspicious.
Why haven't you thrown
me in a dungeon?
You spoke with Tyrion
in this very brothel
on the day that you arrived.
What did you discuss?
You think we conspired together?
The death of my sister.
For which you blame me.
She was raped and murdered
by the Mountain.
The Mountain follows
your orders.
Of course I blame you.
Here I stand unarmed, unguarded.
Should I be concerned?
You are unarmed and unguarded because
you know me better than that.
I am a man of reason.
If I cut your throat today,
I will be drawn
and quartered tomorrow.
Men at war commit
all kinds of crimes
without their
superiors' knowledge.
So you deny involvement
in Elia's murder?
Categorically.
I would like to speak
with the Mountain.
I'm sure he would enjoy
speaking with you.
He might not enjoy it as
much as he thinks he would.
I could arrange
for this meeting.
But you want
something in return.
There will be a trial
for my son.
And as custom dictates,
three judges
will render a verdict.
I will preside.
Mace Tyrell will serve
as the second judge.
I would like you
to be the third.
Why?
Not long ago, the Tyrells
sided with Renly Baratheon.
Declared themselves
enemies of the throne.
Now they are
our strongest allies.
Well, you made
the Tyrell girl a queen.
Asking me to judge at your son's
trial isn't quite as tempting.
I will also invite you
to sit on the small council
to serve as one of the new
king's principal advisors.
I never realized you had such
respect for Dorne, Lord Tywin.
We are not the Seven Kingdoms
until Dorne returns to the fold.
The king is dead. The Greyjoys
are in open rebellion.
A wildling army
marches on the Wall.
And in the East, a Targaryen
girl has three dragons.
Before long, she will
turn her eyes to Westeros.
Only the Dornish
managed to resist
Aegon Targaryen and his dragons.
You're saying you need us?
That must be hard
for you to admit.
We need each other.
You help me serve justice
to the king's assassins
and I will help you
serve justice to Elia's.
( door unlocks )
Podrick.
Apologies for the stench.
I brought you some wine, my
lord, but they took it from me.
A noble effort.
They didn't find
the candles, though.
A quill, some parchment,
duck sausage, almonds,
and some hard cheese.
You're a good lad.
Any word of Shae?
I've heard nothing, my lord.
I suppose that's a good thing.
What are they saying
about me out there?
You're to stand trial
in a fortnight
for murdering the king.
Do you believe
I murdered Joffrey?
No, my lord.
You didn't?
No. Gods, no.
The world is a better
place without him,
but I had nothing to do with it.
I would like to think
if I were arranging
a royal assassination,
I'd plan it in such a way that
I wouldn't be standing there
gawking like a fool
when the king died.
Trial in a fortnight.
Have they announced
the judges yet?
- Your father.
- Of course.
Mace Tyrell.
Who will vote exactly as my
father tells him to vote.
And Prince Oberyn of Dorne.
Oberyn?
Give it to my father.
He never fails to take
advantage of a family tragedy.
I'm supposed to get a list
of names from you, my lord.
Anyone who might testify
on your behalf.
Oh, I can call my own witnesses?
How generous of them.
Very well, my wife.
Sansa.
My lord, she's gone.
- Gone?
- No one's seen her since the wedding.
You don't think she...
No one had more cause
to kill Joffrey than Sansa,
but the girl is no assassin.
Whoever killed the king wanted
me to lose my head for it.
And with my wife's disappearance, it
makes me seem that much more guilty.
- Podrick.
- Yes, my lord?
- They'll be following you now.
- Who will?
I don't know. They.
They. The ominous they.
The man pulling the strings.
Or woman. My father.
Maybe Joffrey
was too much work for him.
Sweet Tommen will be
so much easier to handle.
Whenever something
bad happens to me,
I assume it's my sister
that had a hand in it.
But say what you will of Cersei,
she loves her children.
She is the only one I'm certain had
nothing to do with this murder.
Which makes it unique
as King's Landing murders go.
Any other witnesses, my lord?
Varys could vouch
for me if he dared.
He's already been called
as a witness for the queen.
Of course. Fetch Bronn.
I have a job for him.
I've already asked, my lord.
- They won't let him see you.
- Why not?
They say he's a known cutthroat
and your close associate.
He's under
investigation himself.
And my brother? Will they at
least allow me to see Jaime?
I'll ask, my lord.
There's something else, my lord.
A man, I didn't know his face,
he came to ask if
I'd testify against you.
Said I'd be named
Ser Podrick Payne
if I told the judges you'd bought
a poison called the Strangler.
Ser Podrick Payne?
Has a nice ring to it.
What did you tell him?
I didn't tell them
anything, my lord.
Are you going to
accept their offer?
My lord.
Testifying against me
wasn't a suggestion.
If they can't
tempt you with honey,
they'll choose something
less sweet.
You've been good to me, my lord.
Pod, the trial's in a fortnight.
They'll want an answer
before that.
I already gave them
an answer, my lord.
I will not have you
dying on my behalf.
Do you hear me?
If I have to take
that long walk to
the executioner's block,
I don't want to see
your head already mounted.
- My lord.
- Pod, I am giving you an order.
Go and find my brother.
Tell him I need him.
And get yourself
out of King's Landing
before it's too late.
Pod!
This is farewell.
Farewell, my lord.
( door opens )
Pod.
There has never lived
a more loyal squire.
( door closes )
Boy: Mother says
it's time to eat.
What's she got boiling?
Wait. Wait. Let me guess.
- Potatoes.
Well, no one boils a potato
better than your mom.
Has she got--
Man:
The wildlings!
Guymon!
Hide.
Hide!
( screams )
( shouting, screaming )
( grunting )
You know how to get
to Castle Black?
Yes. Yes.
Those your parents?
Open your eyes.
I'm going to eat them.
Do you hear me?
I'm going to eat your dead mama
and I'm going to eat
your dead papa.
Go tell the crows
at Castle Black.
Yarwyck: We need to teach them a lesson
about the way we deal with their kind.
Men:
Aye! Aye!
Yarwyck:  Three dozen
bodies with slit throats
tossed off the top of the Wall.
- Seems like that would be a good lesson.
- Aye!
If we go after them, we'll be
giving them what they want.
They want to draw us out,
pick us off a few at a time.
We have just over 100 men.
And that's including
stewards and builders.
And me. We can't afford
to lose a single man.
We must remember our
first responsibility.
We are the watchers on the Wall.
There's got to be
a way to protect them.
You're a champion of the
common people, Lord Snow.
What do you say to
Brother Pyp's proposition?
Mance Rayder is coming.
If the wildlings
breach the Wall,
they'll roll over everything
and everyone for 1,000 miles
before they reach an army
that can stop them.
We need to shore up Castle Black
and we need to defend the Wall.
That is our job.
( horn blows )
Rangers returning.
Help him.
Thought you'd have
blue eyes by now.
What took you so long?
- We were held up.
- By what?
Chains.
We were guests of the
mutineers at Craster's Keep.
- And the mutineers stayed?
- They're not going anywhere.
They've got Craster's food
and his wives.
Dolorous Edd:
Poor girls.
Never thought they'd
miss their daddy.
Karl's running things now.
He's the one who put a knife
through Craster's mouth.
We need to ride north
and kill them all.
We just went over this, boy.
- Justice can wait.
- It's not about justice.
I told the wildlings we had over
1,000 men at Castle Black alone.
Karl and the others know
the truth as well as we do.
How long do you think they'll keep
that information to themselves
when the wildlings are peeling
their fingernails off?
Mance has all he needs to crush
us, he just doesn't know it yet.
As soon as he gets
his hands on them, he will.
Then he'll throw
his full strength at us.
And even if every one
of us kills 100 wildlings,
there's still not a thing
we can do to stop them.
I don't think I can
kill 100 wildlings.
( people murmuring )
Daenerys:
Are they attacking?
Jorah:
A single rider.
A champion of Meereen.
They want you to send your
own champion against him.
( cheering )
( horse whinnies )
( speaking Valyrian )
What is he doing?
I believe he means to...
( city crowd
laughing, cheering )
( sighs )
( laughing )
He says that we're an army
of men without man parts.
He claims you are no woman
at all, but a man who...
hides his cock
in his own asshole.
Ignore him, Your Grace.
These are meaningless words.
They're not meaningless if half the city
you intend to take is listening to them.
I have something to say
to the people of Meereen.
First, I will need
this one to be quiet.
Do I have a champion?
_
Your Grace, I've won more single
combats than any man alive.
Which is why you must
remain by my side.
I've been by your side longer
than any of them, Khaleesi.
Let me stand for you
today as well.
You are my most trusted advisor,
my most valued general,
and my dearest friend.
I will not gamble
with your life.
Daario: I was the last
to join your army.
I'm not your general or a
member of your Queensguard
or the commander
of your Unsullied.
My mother was a whore.
I come from nothing.
And before long,
I will return to nothing.
Let me kill this man for you.
Very well.
You have quite an audience.
Make it worth their while.
He is very brave, Your Grace.
Yes, win or lose,
as long as the whole
city is watching.
You sure you don't want a horse?
Daario:  Why would
I want a horse?
Horses are faster than men.
Horses are dumber than men.
( whinnies )
( cheering )
( city crowd shouting )
( shouting )
_
( people screaming )
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0
www.tvsubtitles.net